<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<feedback><data><from>admin</from><content>Feedback section being QA'ed</content><url>http://one.inmobi.com/feedback/</url></data><data><from>Hemant Kumar</from><content>Testing 123</content><url>www.inmobi.com</url></data><data><from>Jimit Doshi</from><content>Guys, this is one of the best stuff i have seen as an intranet tool. I come from infosys with one of the best intranet world wide so had high expectations :) but you guys made this one very neat!&#13;
&#13;
I also want to make a couple of suggestions - &#13;
1. Can we make the # tags searchable or/and have a tag cloud? This way it will be easy to figure out whats trending at inmobi. Its not a burning need..but given we are big and so spread out it will be easy to know wats up! &#13;
2. I went through the group pages...84 groups! Are they all meaningful? if will be good to have a direction on where should one  be or something..&#13;
&#13;
Cheers! </content><url>Url if required...</url></data><data><from>Hemant Kumar</from><content>Test</content><url>test.com</url></data><data><from>Sachin Kanodia</from><content>My Direct report list is not correct, Atul and Amrinder report into Karen Yeo not directly to me. Please get this fixed :-)</content><url/></data><data><from>Tom Bishop</from><content>Loving this new platform - so far it looks and works great! One problem I had was cropping my avatar. I uploaded a jpg.</content><url/></data><data><from>Shrikant Latkar</from><content>test</content><url/></data><data><from>Gaurav Agarwal</from><content>Great Initiative, keep it up!!&#13;
Why is this site so slow? Even the click to 'feedback' takes about 4 seconds.</content><url/></data><data><from>admin</from><content>System thinks i'm admin and shows me Sai's picture.</content><url/></data><data><from>Brittany Solomon</from><content>Is there an option to turn off email alerts? if not, i think that should be made available. Also, are you able to 'tag' other users in posts? I think that should also be a feature :)</content><url/></data><data><from>Ryan Merket</from><content>Can we get email notifications when people post to our Group? A ++ feature would be to allow us to respond to a new post via email as well... </content><url/></data><data><from>Brittany Solomon</from><content>Sonali doesn't work at InMobi anymore</content><url>https://one.inmobi.com/members/sonali/profile/</url></data><data><from>Ryan Merket</from><content>"Promote to admin" removed the member from my group.</content><url/></data><data><from>Ryan Merket</from><content>Nevermind, it looks like the front-end was cached too long.</content><url/></data><data><from>Ryan Merket</from><content>It would be great if we could search the Groups by keyword. </content><url/></data><data><from>Ryan Merket</from><content>I don't understand why Groups like Product Marketing are marked as 'private' -- it would be great to see what they are talking about and get a better understanding of how we are marketing our products. I think team groups should be Public by default. IN fact, I believe nothing should be private unless it's HR, but HR shouldn't be using this tool for sensitive information. Everything else should be open and searchable to allow us to communicate more effectively.</content><url/></data><data><from>Chinmay Deshpande</from><content>The record for Rob Jonas hasn't been updated- he's left the company and everyone under him isn't mapped to his/her new manager.</content><url>https://one.inmobi.com/members/masami-kobayashi/profile/</url></data><data><from>Gary Collins</from><content>I may be missing something, but what is the point of being "Friends" with someone on a company intranet? Surely by definition we are connected to each other as colleagues anyway?&#13;
&#13;
That seems like a bit of a popularity contest to me.</content><url/></data><data><from>Badrinath Mayuranathan</from><content>How does one post anything here?</content><url/></data><data><from>Varun Ramachandra</from><content>Testing Feedback, feedback feature</content><url/></data><data><from>Shrikant Latkar</from><content>Please delete the updates of people becoming friends with each other etc.&#13;
The activity page should only list updates actually posted by the user..e.g. hey we won this great deal in china, check out the pictures from the event last night etc.</content><url/></data><data><from>Shrikant Latkar</from><content>Need to make easy to scroll and find teams on the groups...&#13;
Maybe add a list of hyperlinks on top for different alphabets - A, B, C....Z&#13;
Not sure if the search feature for Teams is working - please test as if I search for a team "Marketing" - it says none exists.</content><url>https://one.inmobi.com/teams/</url></data><data><from>Greg Edgings</from><content>Why is there no App Publish Team?</content><url/></data><data><from>Roland Drewell</from><content>Hi &#13;
&#13;
When you try to add an image, the post button disappears.&#13;
&#13;
All the very best&#13;
&#13;
Roland&#13;
</content><url/></data><data><from>Smita Wadhwa Tyagi</from><content>When the person leaves inmobi, still it profile comes. </content><url/></data><data><from>Sandeep Injarapu</from><content>Where is the 'like' button for Announcements. I wanted to like the MWC Barcelona Announcement. </content><url>https://one.inmobi.com/blog/2013/03/04/mwc-2013/</url></data><data><from>Chinmay Deshpande</from><content>Broken links reporting to these profiles:&#13;
&#13;
https://one.inmobi.com/members/raghu-j/profile/&#13;
https://one.inmobi.com/members/anupama-balasubraman/profile/&#13;
https://one.inmobi.com/members/sachin-kanodia/profile/&#13;
https://one.inmobi.com/members/Ajay-Raut/profile/&#13;
https://one.inmobi.com/members/Humberto-Moreira/profile/&#13;
https://one.inmobi.com/members/paula-kim/profile/&#13;
https://one.inmobi.com/members/jayashree-merwade/profile/&#13;
https://one.inmobi.com/members/jayesh-easwaramony/profile/&#13;
https://one.inmobi.com/members/Vasuta-Agarwal/profile/&#13;
https://one.inmobi.com/members/Youngmin-Lee/profile/&#13;
https://one.inmobi.com/members/srikanth-v/profile/&#13;
https://one.inmobi.com/members/arjun-som/profile/&#13;
</content><url/></data><data><from>Gary Collins</from><content>Hi guys, I'd like to stop Notification emails for status updates. I've checked in the Notification settings, but can't find one for this.</content><url/></data><data><from>Paul Duff</from><content>Firstly: great work on building One InMobi :-)  It's great to have our own setup rather than Podio's one-fits-all approach.&#13;
&#13;
One request/suggestion: using Podio, LinkedIn et al I prefer to receive messages as a daily digest rather than as a continuous stream of messages.  Could we have an option like this in One InMobi please?&#13;
&#13;
Thanks,&#13;
Paul</content><url/></data><data><from>Smita Wadhwa Tyagi</from><content>x-Inmobians profiles are still there</content><url/></data><data><from>Rob Barreca</from><content>How do we opt-out of getting emails for status updates? Also, there are lots of bugs with email encoding, footers, link attachments. See two examples:&#13;
&#13;
A status update has been made by Chris Sanchez&#13;
&#13;
The Wii is set up and in full \"swing\" here in SF thanks to Daniel! [bpfb_images] 697_0.144579001363378884_wii-sf.jpg [/bpfb_images]   Read more..&#13;
&#13;
One InMobi Team&#13;
&#13;
To change the mail subscription setting Click here&#13;
&#13;
------&#13;
&#13;
A status update has been made by Anupama Balasubramanya&#13;
&#13;
Vasuta and Deepak training the GoIB team on mPower Dashbaords.   Read more..&#13;
&#13;
One InMobi Team&#13;
&#13;
To change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click hereTo change the mail subscription setting Click here </content><url/></data><data><from>Brian Mun</from><content>I have all notifications set to NO and I still get emails. Fantastic.</content><url/></data><data><from>Chinmay Deshpande</from><content>Invalid profile "Rob Jonas", contact HR and IT to change reporting manager (listed as manager of John Stoneman)</content><url>https://one.inmobi.com/members/john-stoneman/profile/</url></data><data><from>Smita Wadhwa Tyagi</from><content>Can you please change my reporting manager, invalid profile since long time</content><url>https://one.inmobi.com/members/Smita-Tyagi/profile/</url></data><data><from>tanvi.kapoor</from><content>Hi,&#13;
How can I create a new group or edit the landing page of an existing group? This is for redirecting https://one.inmobi.com/pmm/ to https://sites.google.com/a/inmobi.com/pmm/try &#13;
&#13;
Thanks,&#13;
Tanvi</content><url/></data><data><from>Mayank Talati</from><content>I'm unable to update phone in profile. I can edit my profile, update the phone number, but the Save button is not a clickable button, and hence Save doesn't happen. Would appreciate help in getting this fixed, as the number listed on y pageis now an outdated number that will soon be unreachable.&#13;
&#13;
Regards,&#13;
Mayank Talati</content><url></url></data></feedback>
